Join Tata AIA Life Insurance Business.  Is
a housewife meant only to manage the house
or
can she build her future along with the house?  Hello friends,
I am Yogendra Verma Recruitment
Manager Tata AIA and today I am going to talk to you about
a great opportunity especially for housewives and ladies empowerment.
Why is business perfect for housewives?  See, a housewife has great
skills.  Number one relationship
management.  Number two is patience.  Number Three
Trust Building.  Number four:
Understanding family responsibilities.  And these
qualities are
most important to become a successful life insurance advisor.  Just
think, when you think so much about the security of your home, then
you can also help in the security of others' homes.  Isn't it
?  Let's talk about why choose Tata AIA?
Now the question arises, if you want to do insurance business then
why Tata AIA?  Because friends, the
name Tata itself is the identity of the trust.  Tata
AIA is the second largest private
life insurance company in India.  This
is the company producing the highest MDRT.
And look at the power of the products here.
Here, term plan is the biggest need of every family
and is
available at very reasonable pricing.
You will find the best DULI plans here, which
can help you build wealth and protection,
and there are plenty of guaranteed savings and assured
plans, which
are amazing.  Retirement solutions are also
genuinely available here to secure your future.  The
scope of life insurance is so vast
that it is needed in every household.
How much income can a housewife make?  Now the biggest
question is how much will the income be?  Friends, this is
not a job, there is no salary of any kind here.
This is a commission based business
opportunity in which the more policies you
sell, the more your income will increase.  The commission
here will be from 21% to 45%.  Here,
housewives can also easily join part time and
can easily earn Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per month.  And if you are serious then you can
earn ₹1 lakh annually by becoming MDRT here.
MDRT stands for Million
Dollar Round Table.  This is the
biggest reward and award in life insurance
which is USA recognized
and many women are working on it
and earning good money.
You will also get some extra benefits here.  Along with this
you will get monthly and
quarterly contests.  Domestic
and international fully paid trips will be provided by the company.
In which you
can do world tour.  You can visit multiple countries.
You will get lifetime free training and learning support at company expense.
And most importantly, you will not be left alone.
Three to four managers will
always support you so that you can talk to a professional
life insurance company.
What is the mandatory process here?  So the process
is very simple.  There is one mandatory exam here, the
fee for which will be ₹850.
Anyone can apply all over India.
The exam will be held at a centre near you.  You will have to take two
days of full day compulsory physical branch
training.
This is mandatory before the exam.  And there will be objective type
question answers.  There will be questions of 50 marks.
Passing marks must be 15 marks.
You will have to prepare a list of 50 prospects before the exam.
50 people and has a 100% digital training
platform.  Training will be available from 9:30 am to 10:30 am,
Monday to Saturday.
Training will be available from 8 to 9 in the evening.  5 to 10 sessions will be
available in a month.  After receiving the code, it
is necessary to make a policy in the first month.  It will be necessary to take
12 policies in a year with a premium of Rs 400
so that your code continues.  Let me
talk about women empowerment,
friends, India's
dream is to develop India in 2047 and the agenda is
insurance for every home.  So think, if women do
not come forward then how will every home be secure
?  This business not only gives income but
also gives respect, confidence and empowerment
which is amazing and useful for you.
If you too
want to create your identity and financial freedom by being a housewife.
Why is it the biggest upgrade?  You
are a network marketer.  Is an MLM leader.
So I have brought amazing working for you.
You have formed your team but is the
income permanent?  Join Tata
where the Tata name and 99.13%
claim ratio will keep your team on its toes.
Recruit your team in Tata A Leadership Model and earn unlimited profits.  5%
to 30% is real business.  There
is no hassle in making any member.  There will be an exam fee of ₹850
and a registration fee of ₹5,000.
Free Industrial Trips with Tata
where you can make history.  Only full
time working is available.  Two days of
branch training is mandatory.  Long term
vision is important for you and you have leadership
skills.  You can form a team.
Can trend people.  So don't delay.
Write to Tata AIA Leader on WhatsApp.  I will
guide you genuinely.
Quit MLM.  Become a Tata Corporate Leader and
shape your future.  Hello.  The whole
world is looking towards India today.  Our
country is on its way to becoming the third largest economy in the world.
But do you know
which sector is the brightest star of this Indian growth story?  So that is the
health insurance sector.  Even today,
70% of India's population does not have proper health
insurance cover.  Just imagine, where the
demand is so high and the supply is so low,
how much scope is there for business?  Are you
still chasing old jobs
or want to be a part of a sector
that is going to grow like a rocket for the next 20 years
?  So hello, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager.  I am
helping over 500 partners take advantage of this historic booming sector.
To take advantage of this boom in the health sector, you will need the country's most
trusted company, ICICI LBD.
We are the number one general insurance
company in the country.  When the country grows, the leader will
grow first.  The use of Artificial Intelligence in claim settlement
and 100% digital
model puts us far ahead of others.
Along with 15% to 35% commission on selling health insurance, there is also a sea of ​​passive income like 15%
renewal commission which can
make you successful for generations to come.
Here you get not only money but also respect and the
opportunity for international paid trips.  There are
strict rules for success.
Great work requires discipline for great success.  There are
some clear conditions to join us.  Before getting into the license code,
you will need to
create a prospecting list of 50 people from your network.  No
war
is won without preparation.  After getting the code, it will be
necessary to take a health policy of Rs 15,000 premium in the first month so that your code
becomes active and it is necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code
continues.  Your qualification should be at least 12th
and if your age is between 20 years to 65 years
then you are welcome.  It is
mandatory to give the exam here and the
fee for it is ₹1000 and it takes 10
to 12 days for the exam to come, for which my team will
guide you.  India is changing.  Are
you ready to change your destiny?   The
sector is growing.  The country is growing.
You will not be left only among the spectators, will you?
Join ICC LBA and
become a shareholder in India's progress.  If you
want to secure and prosper your future by joining the mission of Developed India 2047, then
WhatsApp your name and ICC Lobe Health Agent now.  WhatsApp number
is 859540
7616. Please like, share and follow the channel
so that you keep getting better updates.
Hello.  Hello friends, next video
is titled
Why Motor Insurance Agents Become Tata AIA Life Insurance Agent
?  So let's talk about being a motor insurance
agent and let me ask you a question.  If you
insure a vehicle, have you ever
thought of insuring a human life?  Hello friends, I am
Yogendra Verma Recruitment Manager Tata
AIA.  Today's video is especially for those motor
insurance agents who
want to take their business to the next level.
Look at the biggest reality of motor insurance business, friends, motor insurance
is necessary.  But listen to the punch line.  The car is
renewed once a year.  But the
impact of life insurance
lasts for the whole life.  The complexity in motor insurance is
very high.  But the premium
is also limited.  And the client's focus remains
only on the price.  Make it cheaper brother.
But life insurance is a trust based
business.  This is the amazing business of future planning.
Why is an upgrade from Motor to Life necessary?  You already have
clients, car owners, business
owners, working professionals,
female families.  Now imagine all of them
need a term life term plan.  There
is a risk of car accident.  But the
risk to the family's future is the biggest risk.
Term insurance is a basic need of every person.
Why is Tata AIA the brand you trust?   Let's
talk about this also.
Many people have a question in their mind that
why should they join Tata AIA in life insurance
?  So its very simple answer is
Tata equal to trust.  Tata
AIA is the second largest private
life insurance company in India.  Highest
MDRT is one of the leading producer companies.
And the products are such that the client
automatically says that I
want only Tata products.  Be it a term plan
which is the need of every family.  Be it guaranteed
assured plans that provide fixed security
or ULIP plans
that are a great combo of wealth plus protection
and
what to say about retirement planning, pension ready solutions are
available here.  ULIP equal to SIP
plus insurance is a jackpot for motor agents.
Now know the biggest advantage: Motor
clients are already financially aware.
You can now offer them.
ULIP offers SIP like investment option,
mutual fund style wealth creation along with
life cover protection and in this single plan
you get investment insurance plus
future security, that is,
this upgrade becomes super powerful for motor agents
and from here a second source of
earning starts.  You can do this
work easily and flexibly in both part time and full time
options.
In which there is no challenge of any kind.
Whether you do it part time or
full time.  Later on,
you can manage it as a career full time.
You will keep learning here and earning will also
start and continue.  This is amazing
amazing working.  Here
you will get higher commission plus higher income.  Please pay attention.  Let me
first tell you how you will earn here.  This is not any kind of job.
No salary of any kind is
given here.  This is a commission based business
opportunity.  Your income will depend on the number of policies you sell.
The commission ranges from 21% to 45%.  It is possible in part time
and can also be done in full time.
You can earn a minimum of Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per month here and in future, it is possible to
earn Rs 2 lakh, Rs 5 lakh, Rs 10 lakh per month.  By
becoming MDRT, ₹13
lakh can be earned annually here.  And that's what
MDRT Tata is all about.  MDRT
is famous for its culture.  Most of the MDRTs are
made within Tata companies.  And you will
enjoy it even more after hearing about the extra benefits.  Here
you will find monthly and quarterly contests in
which you can qualify for domestic and international
trips in fully paid versions.
You will get lifetime free trainings and learning support here.
You will always have three to four managers to guide you.
You are not alone here.   The
entire Ecos system works with you here.  There are
just some mandatory
procedures here.  You will need to share your basic KYC
documents with us.  Which
I will share with you the list of documents.
In the process, you will have to appear for an exam
which is mandatory and the fee for it will be
₹850.  You can apply for this at the all India level, wherever you are.
The exam will be held
at the nearest centre.  You will have to take two days of full day
compulsory training.
In the local near by branch in which we
will align and here 50 questions will come out of which
you have to pass 15.   It will be
necessary to get 15 marks.  Before the exam, it will be
necessary to prepare a prospecting list of 50 people so that after the exam,
work can be done on what I and my team will
teach you.  It is a 100% digital training
platform.  Here the
training is held in the morning from 9:30 am to 10:30 am Monday
to Saturday through Microsoft Teams.
Training takes place in the evening from
8 to 9 through Zoom meetings. You will get 5 to 10 training sessions
in the evening only.  After receiving the code, it will be
necessary to make a policy in the first month.  It is
mandatory to have a premium of Rs 400 and 12 policies in a year to keep
your code running.  So let me ask you the final question.
As a motor insurance agent, will you limit yourself
to just vehicles or will you
also provide lifetime wealth protection to your clients?  This
is an opportunity to capture the term plan market.  There
is an opportunity to create ULIP wealth
and
move ahead in the retirement planning segment.
You can get higher commission plus tips here.
Better Future Prospective can be yours here.
So if you want to become a motor
insurance agent and make it your next income
pillar, then you have to
WhatsApp me.  Tata AIA Agent my
WhatsApp number is 981826521
or write BOP in DM.  BOP stands for
Business Opportunity Presentation.
I will share its complete PDF with you
on WhatsApp by writing in DM.  And I
am Yogendra Verma Recruitment Manager
Tata AIA 500 Plus Advisors already working on
All Over India basis.  So
please like, share
and follow the channel so that you keep getting updates.
I am talking to you only.   Are
you still flying the flag of the same company
and surviving on low commissions?
Do you know that you can sell
all the insurance companies and all the mutual
funds in India from a single platform.
That too without leaving any old agency.
Yes friends, you won't believe it
but it is possible.  Hello, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager, Bajaj
Capital.  Today, 5000 plus agents from India and abroad are
joining me and creating history.
Bajaj Capital gives you a super
platform where you can manage all the companies like Life, Health, Motor and
Travel
Insurance along with Mutual Funds
together on a single platform.  And the biggest thing is that
you will get the guarantee of highest commission and best trail commission in mutual funds here,
which can be a win-win situation for you.
Those who have come to the channel for the first time,
please follow it.  Otherwise this
important deal will be missed.  It
is very important.  If you
are a fresher in the insurance industry, then there is
no exam, no fees for POS code, the
code will be generated on the same day and you
can start working in 3 days.  And if you
are already an experienced agent, an agent of any IIT company
or already have a
licensed POS code from any broker, then the
marketing code is available here for you.
In which there will be no exam or any fee.
Same day code will be generated and
you can start working after 3 days.  Even if you already have
an IIDA code or broker code,
you can still join Bajaj Capital and
earn extra through marketing code.
No worries, it is 100% legal.
You will not face any kind of challenge or problem.  If I
talk about Bajaj Capital, we have the
trust of 60 years and 1000 plus offices.
Our platform is 100% digital.  If
your customer has a Bajaj Capital
consumer card, he
can purchase any policy on instant EMI.  And now
listen to the topic of earnings.  How much income are you going to get from where
?  If I talk about life insurance,
you can take commission from 25% to 40% to 45%.  If I
talk to health insurance then
you can get 15% to 35% commission.  And
you will also get a good commission on portability here.  If we talk about model insurance,
you will get commission ranging from 2% to 75%.
In this you can do two wheeler, three wheeler,
four wheeler, commercial everything.
Talking about SMA and Group Insurance,
you can get a payout of 5% to 15% and up to 30% here.
In SMA Business.  Talking about travel insurance,
you can get a payout of 20% to 40%.
You are going to get amazing working here.
Not just sales, we provide
amazing claim support and most accurate
timely payouts.  We know what your
hard work is worth.  Whether you are
in India or an NRI, start your financial
journey today.  Don't be part of the crowd.
Become a brand yourself with Bajaj Capital, don't
delay.  This opportunity
is available for a limited time.  Now
call or WhatsApp the number given on the screen.
Write Bajaj Capital Agent Code on WhatsApp.  If you want to
get POS code then write the POS code.   If you want to
get the marketing code then write the marketing code
and it is going to be a win for you.   Do
n't delay.  Get your code today.
Hello thanks.